Angela Valenzuela

Email: angela.v13@outlook.com

Objective

To obtain a position as a UX/UI Web Developer.

Skills & Abilities

Bilingual, detail oriented and organized with ability to multitask.

Independent worker and excellent team player.

Experienced with Adobe applications such as Photoshop, InDesign, Animate and XD Experienced with coding environments such as Brackets for HTML, CSS and Javascript and Github for version control systems.

Experience

Bilingual Customer Care Representative

(February 2018 – Present)

State Farm Insurance / Tempe, AZ

- Managing English and Spanish inbound calls from clients, dealerships, financial institutions and internal business partners.
- Assisting customers with general policy information, transactions and following up with the customer's personal agent when further actions are required.
- Ability to multi-task between client database interfaces and knowledge articles in a high call volume environment.

Teacher Assistant: Intro to Web Authoring

(October 2020 – December 2020)

ASU Ira Fulton Schools of Engineering / Tempe, AZ

- MAssisted Faculty with grading exercises based on basic HTML5 to create webpages, configuring color & text with CSS and applying recommended web design and accessibility practices
- Acted as a source of knowledge for other students based on past coursework experience
- Practiced web development process by reviewing code files, web design practices, & case studies on accessibility

Teacher Assistant: Information Design & Usability

(May 2020 – June 2020)

ASU Ira Fulton Schools of Engineering / Tempe, AZ

 Assisted Faculty with keeping track of student participation in discussions, surveys and case studies

- Acted as a source of knowledge for other students based on past coursework experience
- Practiced UX knowledge and terminology by reviewing surveys, personas, heuristic checklists, case studies and website re-designs

Administrative Coordinator

(August 2014 – December 2018)

Banner Children's Specialists / Mesa, AZ

- Assisted with management of the Pediatric Endocrinology office and Inpatient Pediatric team of Doctors. Assisted with proposals and interviews for incoming Pediatric Doctors.
- Worked with a small team to set up and manage the Fetal Care Program which included working with several Fetal Specialist Doctors in the greater Phoenix area.
- Developed a referral database using Microsoft Access to track intake referrals.

Additional work experience and references available upon request

Education

Arizona State University/ Tempe, AZ

Expected Graduation: Spring 2021

- Bachelors in Applied Science in Web Development
- AIGA Polytechnic Student Club Member
- AIGA Arizona Member

Mesa Community College/ Mesa, AZ

Graduated Summer 2018

• Associates in Applied Science in Web Development